Brotherhood of Railroad Trainmen Records 5149
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Brotherhood of Railroad Trainmen Records
1883-1973
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
5149
153.56 cubic feet
153 linear ft.
Records (documents).
These records deal chiefly with the union during the presidential terms of office of A.F. Whitney (1928-1949), W.P. Kennedy (1949-1963), and Charles Luna (1963-1968).
3336756
Biographical / Historical
The Brotherhood of Railroad Trainmen was founded in 1883 in Oneonta, N.Y. as a protective and insurance organization. By the time of its merger with three other railroad labor unions to form the United Transportation Union in 1969, it had the greatest membership of any of the operating railroad brotherhoods.
The Brotherhood of Railroad Trainmen (BRT) was established to represent members' interests in obtaining a satisfactory contract with management. The first Canadian lodge was established in Moncton, New Brunswick in 1885, and the first Ladies' Auxiliary was organized in Fort Gratiot, Mich. In 1889. These records reflect the union's political and fraternal activities as well as its actions in the areas of collective bargaining, grievances, and railroad and labor legislation. As the largest of the unions which merged to form the United Transportation Union in 1969, the bulk of its then current files formed the basis for the files now held in the merged union's headquarters.
The rail service members of the BRT included conductors and their assistants, dining car stewards, ticket collectors, train baggagemen, brakemen, and train flagmen. The yard service members of the BRT included yardmasters, yard conductors, switchtenders, foremen, flagmen, brakemen, switchmen, car tenders, operators, hump riders, and car operators. In 1933, the BRT organized interstate bus operators, and included them under BRT contracts held with U.S. bus companies.
BRT officers were elected at the Grand Lodge Convention of the Brotherhood, held every 4 years. The principal officers included a president, an assistant to the president, a general secretary-treasurer, Canadian and national legislative representatives, a senior vice-president, BRT representative, and National Railroad Board of Adjustment representative. The BRT had four governing boards: the Board of Directors, Board of Trustees and Insurance, Board of Appeals, and Executive Board.
Scope and Contents
Consists largely of internally circulated BRT publications and documents and those produced by other railroad labor organizations or by railroads.
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: 5021: Brotherhood of Railroad Trainmen Additional Records 5102: Emergency Board No. 129, Long Island Railroad and the Brotherhood of Railroad Trainmen, Locals 517 and 1090, Records 5149 MB: Brotherhood of Railroad Trainmen Memorabilia 5149 P: Brotherhood of Railroad Trainmen Photographs 5348: W.P. Kennedy as President of the Brotherhood of Railroad Trainmen against the Long Island Railroad Company Court Documents 5446: Brotherhood of Railroad Trainmen Ledger 5612: Brotherhood of Railroad Trainmen Moosic Tunnel Lodge no.93 Meeting Minutes 5623: Brotherhood of Railroad Trainmen Legislative Board of New York Files 5631: Brotherhood of Railroad Trainmen Chicago, Milwaukee, St. Paul and Pacific Railroad General Committee File 5647: Brotherhood of Railroad Trainmen Joppa Lodge (Toledo, OH) Minute Books 5894: Brotherhood of Railroad Trainmen Additional Railroad Booklets 6268 P: Joint Committee of Adjustment for the Rock Island System's Order of Railway Conductors and Brotherhood of Railroad Trainmen Photograph 6312 P: Judith Sullivan Kowalczyk Collection of Brotherhood of Railroad Trainmen Photographs 6312 PUBS: Judith Sullivan Kowalczyk Collection of Brotherhood of Railroad Trainmen Publications 6312m: Brotherhood of Railroad Trainmen Annual Report of the Legislative Board 6405 PUBS: William Sharp Collection of The Railroad Trainmen's Journal 6480 MB: Paul Berger Collection of Brotherhood of Railroad Trainmen Memorabilia
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives 227 Ives Hall Tower Road Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183 kheelref@cornell.edu https://catherwood.library.cornell.edu/kheel/
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, August 28, 2013
EAD encoding:
Kheel Staff, March 07, 2019
Railroad conductors -- United States; Railroad law -- United States; Switchmen -- United States; Labor unions -- United States -- Political activity; Railroads -- Employees -- Labor unions -- Canada; Railroads -- Employees -- Labor unions -- United States; Arbitration, Industrial -- Railroads -- Canada; Arbitration, Industrial -- Railroads -- United States; Bargaining unit -- Mediation and conciliation, Industrial -- Canada; Bargaining unit -- Mediation and conciliation, Industrial -- United States; Civil rights -- Law and legislation -- United States; Coal mining industry -- United States -- Safety measures; Collective bargaining -- Railroads -- Canada; Collective bargaining -- Railroads -- United States; Collective labor agreements -- Railroads -- United States; Consumer Protection -- Law and legislation -- United States; Dining car attendants -- United States; Employee fringe benefits -- Railroads -- Canada; Employee fringe benefits -- Railroads -- United States; Railroads -- Employees -- Dismissal of -- United States; Grievance procedures -- Railroads -- Indiana -- Indianapolis; Grievance procedures -- Railroads -- New York (State) -- Syracuse; Grievance procedures -- Railroads -- United States; Hours of labor -- Arbitration, Industrial -- United States; Hump riders -- United States; Health insurance -- Law and legislation -- United States; Unemployment insurance -- Law and legislation -- Pennsylvania; Unemployment insurance -- Law and legislation -- United States; Unemployment insurance -- United States; Job security -- Railroads -- United States; Labor disputes -- Railroads -- United States; Layoffs -- Railroads -- United States; Mediation and conciliation, Industrial -- Railroads -- United States; Open and closed shop -- Law and legislation -- United States; Open and closed shop -- Railroads -- United States; Pensions -- Railroads -- United States; Promotions -- Railroads -- United States; Public welfare -- Law and legislation -- United States; Railroad baggagemen -- United States; Railroad brakemen -- United States; Railroad car retarder operators -- United States; Railroad car tenders -- United States; African American railroad employees; Railroad flagmen -- United States; Railroad ticket collectors -- United States; Railroad trainmen -- United States; Railroad yard operators -- United States; Railroad yardmasters -- United States; Railroads -- Full crew rules -- Alabama; Railroads -- Full crew rules -- Arizona; Railroads -- Full crew rules -- California; Railroads -- Full crew rules -- California; Railroads -- Full crew rules -- Canada; Railroads -- Safety regulations -- United States; Railroads -- Canada -- State supervision; Railroads -- Accidents -- United States -- Statistics; Railroads -- Full crew rules -- Colorado; Railroads -- Full crew rules -- Connecticut; Railroads -- Full crew rules -- Idaho; Railroads -- Full crew rules -- Illinois; Railroads -- Full crew rules -- Indiana; Railroads -- Full crew rules -- Louisiana; Railroads -- Full crew rules -- Massachusetts; Railroads -- Full crew rules -- Minnesota; Railroads -- Full crew rules -- Missouri; Railroads -- Full crew rules -- Nevada; Railroads -- Full crew rules -- New Jersey; Railroads -- Full crew rules -- New Mexico; Railroads -- Full crew rules -- New York (State); Railroads -- Full crew rules -- North Dakota; Railroads -- Full crew rules -- Ohio; Railroads -- Full crew rules -- Pennsylvania; Railroads -- State supervision -- Pennsylvania; Railroads -- Full crew rules -- Rhode Island; Railroads -- Safety regulations -- Pennsylvania; Railroads -- Full crew rules -- Tennessee; Railroads -- Full crew rules -- Texas; Railroads -- Full crew rules -- United States; Railroads -- Safety appliances -- United States; Railroads -- United States -- State supervision; Railroads -- Technological innovations -- United States; Railroads -- Train discontinuance -- United States; Wages -- Railraods -- United States; Railroads -- Full crew rules -- West Virginia; Railroads -- Full crew rules -- Wisconsin; Railroads -- Full crew rules -- Wyoming; Retirement -- Motor bus lines -- United States; Retirement -- Railroads -- United States; Seniority, Employee -- Railroads -- United States; Strikes and lockouts -- Railroads -- United States; Union dues -- Canada; Labor union insurance -- United States; Labor unions -- Mergers -- United States; Trade-union rituals.; Labor unions -- Pennsylvania -- Women's auxiliaries; Railroads -- Employees -- Labor unions -- Canada -- Jurisdictional disputes; Railroads -- Employees -- Labor unions -- Pennsylvania; Railroads -- Employees -- Labor unions -- United States -- Jurisdictional disputes; Railroads -- Employees -- Labor unions -- United States -- Labor union locals; Railroads -- Employees -- Labor unions -- United States -- Labor union locals -- Membership; Labor unions, Black -- Membership -- United States; Labor unions -- United States -- Elections of officials; Labor unions -- United States -- Local unions; Labor unions -- United States -- Membership; Labor unions -- United States -- Women's auxiliaries; Trucking industry -- United States; Wages -- Railroads -- Canada; Wages -- Railroads -- Pennsylvania -- State supervision; Wages -- Railroads -- United States; Wages -- Railroads -- United States -- State supervision; Washington Job Protection Agreement.; Work assignment -- Railroads -- United States; Work rules -- Railroads -- United States; Workers' compensation -- Railroads -- United States; Working conditions -- Railroads -- United States; Akron & Barberton Belt Railroad Company; Akron, Canton and Youngstown Railroad Company; Aliquippa and Southern Railroad; Association of Colored Railway Trainmen and Locomotive Firemen; Atchison, Topeka, and Santa Fe Railway Company; Atlantic Coast Line Railroad Company; Baltimore and Ohio Railroad Company; Bangor and Aroostook Railroad Company; Boston and Maine Railroad; Brotherhood of Railroad Trainmen; Brotherhood of Locomotive Firemen and Enginemen; Brotherhood of Maintenance of Way Employees; Brotherhood of Locomotive Engineers (U.S.); Brotherhood of Railroad Trainmen. General Grievance Committee of the New York Central Lines East; Brotherhood of Railroad Trainmen. Ladies' Auxiliary. Lodge No. 96 (Oneonta, N.Y.); Brotherhood of Railroad Trainmen. Ladies' Auxiliary. Lodge No. 122; Brotherhood of Railroad Trainmen. Ladies' Auxiliary. Lodge No. 595 (Albuquerque, N.M.); Brotherhood of Railroad Trainmen. Lodge No. 105. (Oil City, Pa.); Brotherhood of Railroad Trainmen. Lodge No. 143 (Syracuse, N.Y.); Brotherhood of Railroad Trainmen. Lodge No. 187 (Buffalo, N.Y.); Brotherhood of Railroad Trainmen. Lodge No. 311 (Mechanicsville); Brotherhood of Railroad Trainmen. Lodge No. 927 (Cleveland, Ohio); Brotherhood of Railroad Trainmen. Lodge No. 1000 (Indianapolis, Ind.); Brotherhood of Railroad Trainmen. Pennsylvania State Legislative Board; Brotherhood of Sleeping Car Porters; Canada. Board of Conciliation; Canada. Full Crew Law; Canada. Railway War Board; Canadian National Railways; Canadian Pacific Railway Company; Chicago and North Western Railway Company; Chicago, Burlington & Quincy Railroad Company; Chicago Great Western Railway Company (1940-1968); Chicago, North Shore and Milwaukee Railroad; Chicago, Rock Island, and Pacific Railroad Company (1948- ); Cleveland Union Terminals Company; Colorado and Southern Railway; Cumberland Valley Railroad Company; Delaware and Hudson Railroad Corporation; Delaware, Lackawanna and Western Railroad Company; Denver and Rio Grande Western Railroad Company; Des Moines Union Railroad; Erie Railroad Company; Erie-Lackawanna Railroad Company; Grand Trunk Pacific Railway Company; Great Northern Railway Company (U.S.); Gulf, Colorado, and Santa Fe Railroad; Gulf, Mobile and Ohio Railroad Company; Illinois Central Railroad Company; Indiana Harbor Belt Railroad Company; Iowa Central Railway; Joint General Grievance Committee of the Order of Railway Conductors and the Brotherhood of Railroad Trainmen of the New York Central Lines East; Kansas City Southern Railway Company; Lackawanna and Wyoming Valley Railroad; Lehigh and New England Railroad; Lehigh Valley Railroad Company; Long Island Rail Road; Louisville and Nashville Railroad Company; Maine Central Railroad Company; Michigan Central Railroad; Minneapolis & St. Louis Railroad; Minneapolis and St. Paul Railroad; Minneapolis, St. Paul & Sault Ste. Marie Railway Company; Missouri-Kansas-Texas Railroad; Missouri, Oklahoma & Gulf Railway Company; Missouri Pacific Railroad Company; Monongahela Railway Company; Nashville, Chattanooga, and St. Louis Railway; New York Central Railroad Company; New York, Chicago, and St. Louis Railway Company; New York, New Haven and New Hartford Railroad. Old Colony Division; New York, Ontario, and Western Railway Co.; Norfolk and Western Railway Company; Norfolk, Portsmouth and Belt Railroad; Northern Pacific Railroad Company; Operating Brotherhoods Protective Association; Order of Railroad Telegraphers (U.S.); Order of Railway Conductors and Brakemen; Order of Railway Conductors of America; Oregon and Washington Railroad and Navigation Company; Oregon Shortline Railroad; Pacific Electric Railway Company; Panhandle & Santa Fe Railway; Pennsylvania League for Consumer Protection; Pennsylvania Railroad; Pere Marquette Railway; Philadelphia & Reading Railroad Co.; Pittsburgh and Lake Erie Railroad Company; Quebec Central Railroad; Railway Association of Canada; Railway Labor Executives Association; Reading Company; Rutland Railroad Company; San Pedro, Los Angeles & Salt Lake Railroad Company; Southern Pacific Company; Southern Railway (U.S.); St. Joseph & Grand Island Railway; St. Louis Southwestern Railway Company; Supreme Council of United Orders of Railway Employees; Switchmen's Union of North America; Terminal Railroad Association of St. Louis; Texas & Pacific Railway; Trainmen's Political Education League (Canada); Trainmen's Political Education League (U.S.); Trinity and Brazos Valley Railway Company; Ulster & Delaware Railroad; Union Pacific Railway Company; United Brotherhood of Railway Employees; United States. Federal Railroad Administration; United States. National Mediation Board; United States. National Railroad Adjustment Board; United States. National Railway Labor Panel; United States. National War Labor Board (1942-1945); United Transportation Union; Virginia Railroad; Wabash Railroad; West Pullman and Southern Railroad Company; Western Association of General Committees; Western Maryland Railway Company; Western Pacific Railroad Company; Abel, I. Walter. 1908-; Balt, William L., Jr.; Beattie, Donald S.; Boyer, Harry; Caffey, J.A.; Chase, W. E. B.; Chesser, Al H.; Duff, James H. (James Henderson), 1883-1969; Elnes, W. T.; Esposito, Francis J.; Faulkner, L. K.; Fox, Michael; Haddix, W.; Innis, W. G.; Keenan, Joseph D.; Kennedy, William P. (William Parker), 1892-1968; Leader, George M.; Leighty, G. E.; Luna, Charles, 1906-; Meany, George, 1894-1980; Minehart, Thomas; Murphy, M. J.; Price, W. E.; Price, Wolfgang S., 1930-; Reilly, J. M.; Reinhard, J. W.; Roberts, G. W.; Rogers, G. W.; Roosevelt, Franklin D. (Franklin Delano), 1882-1945; See, Harry; Shapp, Milton J., 1912-1994; Shearer, J. L.; Shearer, Thomas Park; Sludden, C. J.; Stewart, C. G.; Toohey, Edward F.; Weil, W. J.; Whitney, Alexander F. (Alexander Fell), 1873-1949
3336756
- 1883-1889 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- 1901-1909 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- 1911-1913 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- 1916-1925 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- 1928-1931 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- 1900 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- 1935-1939 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- 1946-1950 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- 1954-1960 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- 1964 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- 1902-1903 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- 1915-1917 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- 1899-1901 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- January 1922 (Box 1, Folder 14)
- 1924-1925 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- 1926-1927 (Box 1, Folder 16)
- 1933-1934 (Box 1, Folder 17)
- 1935-1936 (Box 1, Folder 18)
- 1937-1939 (Box 1, Folder 19)
- 1930-1932 (Box 1, Folder 20)
- 1904-1906 (Box 1, Folder 21)
- 1907-1909 (Box 1, Folder 22)
- 1911-1914 (Box 1, Folder 23)
- 1918-1921 (Box 1, Folder 24)
- 1928-1930 (Box 1, Folder 25)
- 1939-1940 (Box 2, Folder 1)
- 1941-1942 (Box 2, Folder 2)
- 1942-1943 (Box 2, Folder 3)
- 1943 (Box 2, Folder 4)
- 1944 (Box 2, Folder 5)
- 1945 (Box 2, Folder 6)
- 1946 (Box 2, Folder 7)
- 1947 (Box 2, Folder 8)
- 1948 (Box 2, Folder 9)
- 1949 (Box 2, Folder 10)
- 1950 (Box 2, Folder 11)
- 1951 (Box 2, Folder 12)
- 1952 (Box 2, Folder 13)
- 1953 (Box 2, Folder 14)
- 1954 (Box 2, Folder 15)
- 1955 (Box 2, Folder 16)
- 1956 (Box 2, Folder 17)
- 1957 (Box 2, Folder 18)
- 1958: Jan.-Sept. (Box 2, Folder 19)
- 1958: Oct.-Dec. (Box 2, Folder 20)
- 1959 (Box 2, Folder 21)
- 1961: Jan.-July (Box 3, Folder 1)
- 1961-1962 (Box 3, Folder 2)
- 1962: Jan.-May (Box 3, Folder 3)
- 1962 (Box 3, Folder 4)
- 1963 (Box 3, Folder 5)
- 1964 (Box 3, Folder 6)
- 1965 (Box 3, Folder 7)
- 1966 (Box 3, Folder 8)
- 1967-1968 (Box 3, Folder 9)
- PSF Canada Wage Rule Information (Box 4, Folder 1)
- PSA Canada Wage Rule Information, Part 2 (Box 4, Folder 2)
- PSA Canada Wage Rule Information, Part 3 (Box 4, Folder 3)
- RLEA [Retirement Benefits]- 1965 (Box 4, Folder 4)
- RLEA [Retirement Benefits]- 1965, Part 2 (Box 4, Folder 5)
- RLEA [Retirement Benefits]- 1965, Part 3 (Box 4, Folder 6)
- Benefits (Hospital and Surgical Care)- 1956 (Box 4, Folder 7)
- Benefits (Mothers' Allowances- Canada)- 1954 (Box 4, Folder 8)
- Benefits (Chiropractic)- 1955-58 (Box 4, Folder 9)
- Benefits (Chiropractic)- 1955 (Box 4, Folder 10)
- Benefits (Chiropractic)- 1955, Part 2 (Box 4, Folder 11)
- Benefits (Chiropractic)- 1955 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  Scope and Contents
  Includes Public Affairs Institute Report
- Benefits (Chiropractic)- 1951-1955 (Box 4, Folder 13)
- Benefits (e.g. Insurance) c. 1964 (Box 4, Folder 14)
- Federal Employers' Liability Act (Box 4, Folder 15)
- R.S. Payton Personal Injury (1956-58) (Box 4, Folder 16)
- Benefits- RR Retirement Act (Box 4, Folder 17)
- Benefits- RR Retirement Act c. 1959-60 (Box 4, Folder 18)
- Benefits- RR Retirement Act c. 1961-2 (Box 4, Folder 19)
- PSF Conventions: 1935 Convention (Box 4, Folder 20)
- PSF Conventions: Conventional Lodges 11-496 (Box 4, Folder 21)
- 1950 Convention: Lodges 506-1049 (Box 4, Folder 22)
- PSF Conventions: Constitution Committee c.1950, Part 1 (Box 5, Folder 1)
- PSF Conventions: Constitution Committee c.1950, Part 2 (Box 5, Folder 2)
- PSF Conventions: Actions Taken at 1950 Convention, c. 1951-54 (Box 5, Folder 3)
- Conventions: Delegate Elections by Lodges (Box 5, Folder 4)
- Delegates Elected to 29th Convention (Box 5, Folder 5)
- Delegated Elected to 29th Convention: Lodges 1-499 (Box 5, Folder 6)
- PSF Conventions: Resolutions & Reports Adopted by the 29th Convention (Box 5, Folder 7)
- Joint Relations Committee (Box 5, Folder 8)
- PSF Conventions- 1950 Convention, Part 1 (Box 5, Folder 9)
- PSF Conventions- 1950 Convention, Part 2 (Box 5, Folder 10)
- PSF Conventions- 1950 Convention, Part 3 (Box 5, Folder 11)
- PSF Conventions- 1950 Convention, Part 4 (Box 5, Folder 12)
- PSF Conventions- 1950 Convention, Part 5 (Box 5, Folder 13)
- PSF Conventions- 1950 Convention, Part 6 (Box 5, Folder 14)
- PSF Conventions- 1950 Convention, Part 7 (Box 5, Folder 15)
- Convention- 1954 (Box 6, Folder 1)
- Age Limit 65-70 (Box 6, Folder 2)
- Credential Committee (Box 6, Folder 3)
- Delegate Instructions and Ballots (Box 6, Folder 4)
- General Chairmen and Legislative Rep. Authorized to Attend Convention (Box 6, Folder 5)
- Grand Lodge Officers Excused from Convention to Return Home (Box 6, Folder 6)
- Legislative Committee- U.S. Legal Assessment (Box 6, Folder 7)
- Moving Brotherhood Office Equipment to Miami, FL and Return Convention (Box 6, Folder 8)
- Negro Question Re: 1954 BRT Convention (Box 6, Folder 9)
- Proceedings- Minutes (Box 6, Folder 10)
- Promotion Committee (Box 6, Folder 11)
- Refunds- Pullman Trains (Box 6, Folder 12)
- Resolutions Committee, No. 3 (Canada) (Box 6, Folder 13)
- Ritual Committee (Box 6, Folder 14)
- Trainmen News (Box 6, Folder 15)
- Various Matters to Be Taken Up at Convention (Box 6, Folder 16)
- Visitors- Expected Speakers- Interview with W.P.K. (Box 6, Folder 17)
- Wage and Rules (Box 6, Folder 18)
- PSF Conventions- 1957: Appeal to Bd. Of Directors (Box 6, Folder 19)
- PSF Convention- 1958: Correspondence c. 1957 (A) (Box 6, Folder 20)
- PSF Convention- 1958: Correspondence c. 1957 (B) (Box 6, Folder 21)
- PSF Convention- 1958: Correspondence 1956-59 (A) (Box 6, Folder 22)
- PSF Convention- 1958: Correspondence 1956-59 (B) (Box 6, Folder 23)
- PSF Convention- 1958: Correspondence 1956-59 (C) (Box 6, Folder 24)
- Legal Dept. File Re: 1958 Convention (A) (Box 6, Folder 25)
- Legal Dept. File Re: 1958 Convention (B) (Box 6, Folder 26)
- Legal Dept. File Re: 1958 Convention (C) (Box 6, Folder 27)
- Postponement (A) (Box 6, Folder 28)
- Postponement (B) (Box 6, Folder 29)
- Postponement (D) (Box 6, Folder 30)
  Folder C is missing.
- Proposed Postponement- Protests Against (Box 6, Folder 31)
- Proposed Postponement- Violation of Section 4 (Box 6, Folder 32)
- PSF Conventions- 1958 Convention: c. 1957 (A) (Box 6, Folder 33)
- PSF Conventions- 1958 Convention: c.1957 (B) (Box 6, Folder 34)
- PSF Conventions- 1958 Convention: c. 1957 (C) (Box 6, Folder 35)
- BRT Essay Contest, Part 1 (Box 7, Folder 1)
- BRT Essay Contest, Part 2 (Box 7, Folder 2)
- 1960-69 (Box 7, Folder 3)
- PSF- Financial Reports: Misc. Vouchers and Memos (Box 7, Folder 4)
- Expenses and Bills (Box 7, Folder 5)
- Eco. Power Concentration (Box 7, Folder 6)
- Financial Reports- Local Treasurers (Box 7, Folder 7)
- PSF Financial Reports Re: ICC Finance Docket #21500-21595 (Box 7, Folder 8)
- PSF Financial Reports: Monthly Reports (Box 7, Folder 9)
- PSF Financial Reports: Monthly Reports 1956-57 (Box 7, Folder 10)
- ICC Finance Docket (NYC/P+LE RR), 1961 (Box 7, Folder 11)
- Monthly Reports, 1958-1959 (Box 7, Folder 12)
- ICC Finance Docket # 21200-21298: NYC RR (A) (Box 7, Folder 13)
- ICC Finance Dockets #21200-21298: NYC RR (B) (Box 7, Folder 14)
- ICC Finance Docket #21160, 21161, 21237, 21238 (Box 7, Folder 15)
- Monthly Reports- c.1960-63 (Box 7, Folder 16)
- ICC Finance Docket #21114 (Box 7, Folder 17)
- ICC Finance Dockets #21100-2199 (A) (Box 7, Folder 18)
- ICC Finance Dockets #21100-21199 (Box 7, Folder 19)
- ICC FD 21620, 21613 (Box 8, Folder 1)
- ICC FD 21606-21608, 21115 (Box 8, Folder 2)
- ICC FD 21624-21675 (Box 8, Folder 3)
- ICC FD 21300-21399 (Box 8, Folder 4)
- ICC FD 21394-21399 (Box 8, Folder 5)
- ICC FD 21676-21695 (Box 8, Folder 6)
- ICC FD 21366, 21391 (Box 8, Folder 7)
- ICC FD 21329, 21366, 23229, 23230 (Box 8, Folder 8)
- ICC FD 206081, 21350, 21326, 21329, 23229, 23230 (Box 8, Folder 9)
- ICC FD 21325-213257 (Box 8, Folder 10)
- ICC FD 22000-22008 (A) (Box 8, Folder 11)
- ICC FD 22000-22008 (B) (Box 8, Folder 12)
- ICC FD 21742-21799 (A) (Box 8, Folder 13)
- ICC FD 21742-21799 (B) (Box 8, Folder 14)
- ICC FD 22004-22009 (Box 8, Folder 15)
- ICC FD 21800-21899 (A) (Box 8, Folder 16)
- ICC FD 21800-21899 (B) (Box 8, Folder 17)
- ICC FD 21800-21899 (Box 8, Folder 18)
- ICC FD 22468, 22479, 22481-22485, 22490 (Box 9, Folder 1)
- ICC FD 22465-23455 (Box 9, Folder 2)
- ICC FD 22305-22314 (Box 9, Folder 3)
- ICC FD 21325-21327, 22314-22329 (Box 9, Folder 4)
- ICC FD 21840-22422 (Box 9, Folder 5)